[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "What was going through your minds?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "going", "through", "your", "minds", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "The first moment that I think something really was critically wrong was there was an off-duty pilot sitting a few rows behind and the flight attendants asked him to step into the cockpit.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "first", "moment", "that", "I", "think", "something", "really", "was", "critically", "wrong", "was", "there", "was", "an", "off-duty", "pilot", "sitting", "a", "few", "rows", "behind", "and", "the", "flight", "attendants", "asked", "him", "to", "step", "into", "the", "cockpit", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "What do you think had happened to him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "had", "happened", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "I really can't say what happened to him but I can tell you what I observed.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "really", "ca", "n't", "say", "what", "happened", "to", "him", "but", "I", "can", "tell", "you", "what", "I", "observed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "If you hadn't been, it could have been a very, very situation, couldn't it?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "had", "n't", "been", ",", "it", "could", "have", "been", "a", "very", ",", "very", "situation", ",", "could", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "RB", ",", "RB", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 86, "question": "I would imagine there was just huge panic, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "would", "imagine", "there", "was", "just", "huge", "panic", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 87, "answer": "That's an excellent question.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "an", "excellent", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "Yes, and Tony, once the plane landed, what was the next move?", "question_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "and", "Tony", ",", "once", "the", "plane", "landed", ",", "what", "was", "the", "next", "move", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CC", "NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Well, we were physically on top of this guy for about 20 minutes while the plane was descending.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "were", "physically", "on", "top", "of", "this", "guy", "for", "about", "20", "minutes", "while", "the", "plane", "was", "descending", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tony"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 105, "question": "I mean was there a moment when you guys were sitting on top of him, Paul, when given his size and his crazed condition, did you fear that he could break free and that, you know, everyone's lives would be in serious danger?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "was", "there", "a", "moment", "when", "you", "guys", "were", "sitting", "on", "top", "of", "him", ",", "Paul", ",", "when", "given", "his", "size", "and", "his", "crazed", "condition", ",", "did", "you", "fear", "that", "he", "could", "break", "free", "and", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "everyone", "'s", "lives", "would", "be", "in", "serious", "danger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "POS", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 106, "answer": "Piers, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Paul"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 131, "question": "But what were your feelings as you came off?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "were", "your", "feelings", "as", "you", "came", "off", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 132, "answer": "You know, I have to say I think we're really just very thankful.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "have", "to", "say", "I", "think", "we", "'re", "really", "just", "very", "thankful", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 138, "question": "One is, have you had any drink coupons from JetBlue to say thank you yet?", "question_tokens": ["One", "is", ",", "have", "you", "had", "any", "drink", "coupons", "from", "JetBlue", "to", "say", "thank", "you", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "VBZ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 139, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["JetBlue"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "I mean, have you heard from anybody high up at the airline?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "have", "you", "heard", "from", "anybody", "high", "up", "at", "the", "airline", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "No, not as of yet.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "as", "of", "yet", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "What is your sense from the legal perspective of the way things are unfurling here?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "sense", "from", "the", "legal", "perspective", "of", "the", "way", "things", "are", "unfurling", "here", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Today the individual mandate was heard.", "answer_tokens": ["Today", "the", "individual", "mandate", "was", "heard", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Martin"]}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "What is your personal emotional reaction to what they're going through and if I can ask you a difficult question, if this was your son who have been killed in these circumstances, would you not want to at least see an arrest and a legal process to go through that could determine the truth of what happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "personal", "emotional", "reaction", "to", "what", "they", "'re", "going", "through", "and", "if", "I", "can", "ask", "you", "a", "difficult", "question", ",", "if", "this", "was", "your", "son", "who", "have", "been", "killed", "in", "these", "circumstances", ",", "would", "you", "not", "want", "to", "at", "least", "see", "an", "arrest", "and", "a", "legal", "process", "to", "go", "through", "that", "could", "determine", "the", "truth", "of", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "IN", "JJS", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "LIVER: You know, first of all, my heart goes out to the Martin family because I have an 18-year-old son.", "answer_tokens": ["LIVER", ":", "You", "know", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "my", "heart", "goes", "out", "to", "the", "Martin", "family", "because", "I", "have", "an", "18-year-old", "son", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "What do you really believe happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "really", "believe", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Well, I believe what George has told me happened.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "believe", "what", "George", "has", "told", "me", "happened", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 283, "question": "I mean, does he feel that -- when did you last speak to George?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "does", "he", "feel", "that", "--", "when", "did", "you", "last", "speak", "to", "George", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", ":", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 284, "answer": "Yesterday.", "answer_tokens": ["Yesterday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Does he feel it would have been easier now for him to have been arrested?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "he", "feel", "it", "would", "have", "been", "easier", "now", "for", "him", "to", "have", "been", "arrested", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "JJR", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "I haven't spoken with him about that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "n't", "spoken", "with", "him", "about", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["100 percent"]}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "But the fact that somebody could shoot a 17-year-old boy who is armed with just a pack of Skittles and not even be arrested, doesn't that say to you there's something wrong fundamentally with that law and it ought to be amended?", "question_tokens": ["But", "the", "fact", "that", "somebody", "could", "shoot", "a", "17-year-old", "boy", "who", "is", "armed", "with", "just", "a", "pack", "of", "Skittles", "and", "not", "even", "be", "arrested", ",", "does", "n't", "that", "say", "to", "you", "there", "'s", "something", "wrong", "fundamentally", "with", "that", "law", "and", "it", "ought", "to", "be", "amended", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VB", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "If that was all that this story was, I agree with you 100 percent.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "that", "was", "all", "that", "this", "story", "was", ",", "I", "agree", "with", "you", "100", "percent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "VBZ", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "With hindsight, that was clearly a catastrophic error of judgment on his part, wasn't it?", "question_tokens": ["With", "hindsight", ",", "that", "was", "clearly", "a", "catastrophic", "error", "of", "judgment", "on", "his", "part", ",", "was", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "And here's what the evidence is going to show.", "answer_tokens": ["And", "here", "'s", "what", "the", "evidence", "is", "going", "to", "show", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party", "Club"]}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Who are the cannibals?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "are", "the", "cannibals", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "The cannibals are the Tea Party, are the Club for Growth.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "cannibals", "are", "the", "Tea", "Party", ",", "are", "the", "Club", "for", "Growth", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "Isn't that the reality?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "n't", "that", "the", "reality", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "Piers, I'm not talking about the dogs.", "answer_tokens": ["Piers", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "talking", "about", "the", "dogs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "Well, where are these bodies buried?", "question_tokens": ["Well", ",", "where", "are", "these", "bodies", "buried", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "These bodies are buried in ended careers.", "answer_tokens": ["These", "bodies", "are", "buried", "in", "ended", "careers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "Is it time for Newt Gingrich or Ron Paul or Rick Santorum to throw the towel in?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "time", "for", "Newt", "Gingrich", "or", "Ron", "Paul", "or", "Rick", "Santorum", "to", "throw", "the", "towel", "in", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "I think it is plainly going to be Romney as the nominee.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "is", "plainly", "going", "to", "be", "Romney", "as", "the", "nominee", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich", "Ron Paul", "Rick Santorum"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "What was the purpose in writing it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "purpose", "in", "writing", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "Any time you're around greatness, like I was for six years, and you see it at close quarters, you're asked about it.", "answer_tokens": ["Any", "time", "you", "'re", "around", "greatness", ",", "like", "I", "was", "for", "six", "years", ",", "and", "you", "see", "it", "at", "close", "quarters", ",", "you", "'re", "asked", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 455, "question": "I mean, as far as coach and player goes, it doesn't get much closer than that, does it?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "as", "far", "as", "coach", "and", "player", "goes", ",", "it", "does", "n't", "get", "much", "closer", "than", "that", ",", "does", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CC", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 456, "answer": "That's a lot of time to spend with a player.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "lot", "of", "time", "to", "spend", "with", "a", "player", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "What did you make of him as a man?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "him", "as", "a", "man", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "Well, very complex.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "very", "complex", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "How do you respond to that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "respond", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Well, I'm certainly not the first coach that's ever written a book.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "certainly", "not", "the", "first", "coach", "that", "'s", "ever", "written", "a", "book", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 485, "question": "What's your response to him?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "response", "to", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 486, "answer": "Well, I mean, those rules are not written rules.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "those", "rules", "are", "not", "written", "rules", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 503, "question": "So I'm going to make money out of his intimate life in the way you have done?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "make", "money", "out", "of", "his", "intimate", "life", "in", "the", "way", "you", "have", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 504, "answer": "No, not in any way, shape or form.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "in", "any", "way", ",", "shape", "or", "form", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tiger"], "PERSON": ["Mark Steinberg"]}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBN", "PRP", "CC", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "''", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 530, "question": "Could you quite believe what you were hearing when all these stories began to come out?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "quite", "believe", "what", "you", "were", "hearing", "when", "all", "these", "stories", "began", "to", "come", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "WRB", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 531, "answer": "No, I couldn't because the first, you know, inkling that there might be a problem was Mark Steinberg, Tiger's agent, called me and told me that there was going to be an article coming out in \"The National Enquirer,\" but that it wasn't true.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "could", "n't", "because", "the", "first", ",", "you", "know", ",", "inkling", "that", "there", "might", "be", "a", "problem", "was", "Mark", "Steinberg", ",", "Tiger", "'s", "agent", ",", "called", "me", "and", "told", "me", "that", "there", "was", "going", "to", "be", "an", "article", "coming", "out", "in", "``", "The", "National", "Enquirer", ",", "''", "but", "that", "it", "was", "n't", "true", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "Would you have done if you had known?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "done", "if", "you", "had", "known", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "I don't think it would be my place necessarily as a coach, but it would be my place, I feel like, as a friend.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "would", "be", "my", "place", "necessarily", "as", "a", "coach", ",", "but", "it", "would", "be", "my", "place", ",", "I", "feel", "like", ",", "as", "a", "friend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Do you feel that he's changed at all since the scandal?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "he", "'s", "changed", "at", "all", "since", "the", "scandal", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "You know, I think he's probably softened some.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "he", "'s", "probably", "softened", "some", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120327pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "Could he win the Masters this year, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "he", "win", "the", "Masters", "this", "year", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "He's definitely striking the ball well.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "'s", "definitely", "striking", "the", "ball", "well", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]